So we've talked about the most important stuff within this this lesson about numbers and dates about
所以我们在本课中讨论了关于数字和日期的最重要的东西
symbols.
符号。
These are the things you see most often but I feel like because this is the class on technical description
这些是你最常看到的东西，但我觉得因为这是技术描述课
and that we're trying to get through this stuff which is what many people would say a little less interesting
并且我们正在努力解决这些问题，很多人会说这不太有趣
it's important to make sure that you're clear on one point about the difference between abbreviations
重要的是要确保您清楚地了解缩写之间的区别
and acronyms.
和首字母缩略词。
What's an abbreviation an abbreviation is when you have one word that is shorthand.
什么是缩略语 缩略语是指你有一个单词是速记的。
One example would be S T which is the abbreviation of the word street one word shortened one you probably
一个例子是 S T，它是街道一词的缩写，你可能会缩短一个词
know D R is the abbreviation of the word doctor or sometimes drive sometimes P H L is the abbreviation
知道 D R 是医生这个词的缩写，有时是驱动器，有时是 P H L 是缩写
of philosophy e t c is the abbreviation of the word et cetera et cetera or etc. People say both et cetera
ofphilosophy e t c 是 et cetera et cetera or etc 这个词的缩写。人们说 both et cetera
et cetera.
等等。
Now notice that when we write abbreviations we usually have this period at the end to market but sometimes
现在请注意，当我们编写缩写词时，我们通常在市场结束时有这个时期，但有时
it becomes so common that it's basically the only thing we say and we often get rid of that if that's
它变得如此普遍，以至于它基本上是我们唯一说的话，如果那是我们经常会摆脱它
the case.
案子。
Example this one we often just say now an app and we don't even write the period anymore.
例如这个我们现在经常说的应用程序，我们甚至不再写句号了。
This is short for application because it's so commonly said as app now instead of application we often
这是应用程序的缩写，因为它现在通常被称为应用程序而不是我们经常使用的应用程序
just get rid of that period and say app and now we say things like apps.
只是摆脱那个时期并说应用程序，现在我们说应用程序之类的东西。
What do you do for a living.
你靠什么谋生。
Oh I build apps I build apps.
哦，我构建应用程序我构建应用程序。
OK.
好的。
So that's very common and because it's so common we get rid of the period.
所以这很常见，因为它很常见，我们摆脱了这个时期。
Now what about an acronym an acronym is a way to shorten things but each letter is capital capitalized
现在首字母缩略词怎么样 首字母缩略词是一种缩短事物的方法，但每个字母都大写
and each letter stands for or represents its own word for example and B A or BBC or a T M A.T.M. for
每个字母代表或代表自己的单词，例如 B A 或 BBC 或 T M A.T.M.为了
example stands for automatic teller machine.
示例代表自动柜员机。
One mistake people often make is that they'll say I need to go to the A.T.M. machine what people should
人们经常犯的一个错误是他们会说我需要去 A.T.M.机器人们应该做什么
say is I need to go to the A.T.M. not I need to go to the A.T.M. machine because if you're saying that
比如说我需要去 A.T.M.我不需要去自动柜员机。机器，因为如果你这么说
you're saying automatic teller machine machine I've made that mistake before as well but it's it's something
你是说自动取款机机器我以前也犯过这个错误，但它的东西
that you'll hear quite often.
你会经常听到。
So each first letter is used in the word and some of them are really long like scuba if you hear people
所以每个第一个字母都用在这个词中，如果你听到人们的话，其中一些真的很长，就像 scuba
say I'm going to go scuba diving.
说我要去潜水。
That's a common word means you're going to go underwater and breathe underwater.
这是一个常见的词，意思是你要去水下，在水下呼吸。
But because each letter is kind of a long thing it's much easier just to say scuba scuba gear scuba
但是因为每个字母都比较长，所以说 scuba scuba gear scuba 要容易得多
diving write great scuba spot or a location for scuba diving.
潜水写伟大的水肺潜水地点或水肺潜水的地点。
So that's the difference between acronyms and abbreviations since we've talked about abbreviations we
这就是首字母缩写词和缩写词之间的区别，因为我们已经讨论过缩写词，我们
should just very quickly go over addresses because you do see addresses from time to time so you'll
应该很快检查地址，因为您确实会不时看到地址，因此您将
typically have the street first and then the building and then sometimes another part of the location
通常首先是街道，然后是建筑物，有时是位置的另一部分
and we might then under that have the state and what's called the zip code of the city the state and
然后我们可能会在下面有州和所谓的城市邮政编码 州和
the zip code or if it's in Canada or the province the city the province and the zip code zip code tells
邮政编码，或者如果它在加拿大或该省城市该省和邮政编码邮政编码告诉
you where in the world or where in the country it is.
你在世界的什么地方或它在国家的什么地方。
It's a number.
这是一个数字。
So two Bay s t means street 200 Bay Street.
所以两个 Bay s t 表示 200 Bay Street 街。
Sweet sweet.
甜甜的。
It's kind of like room 180 sometimes 180 instead of one hundred eighty.
有点像 180 号房间，有时是 180 号而不是 180 号。
Royal Court CTC o u r t.
皇家法院 CTC o u r t。
OK so this is how we would read that 200 Bay Street Suite 180 royal court.
好的，这就是我们如何解读 200 Bay Street Suite 180 皇家宫廷。
Pretty simple.
很简单。
This one apartment two building 18 apartment two building so AAPT is Apartment B L DG The Site B L G.D.
这栋公寓二楼 18 公寓二楼所以 AAPT 是 Apartment B L DG The Site B L G.D.
So for example in England and America things might be abbreviated a little differently.
因此，例如在英国和美国，事情的缩写可能会有所不同。
So apartment two building 18 5 8 9 9.
所以公寓二号楼 18 5 8 9 9。
So if it's an address you don't need to say five thousand eight hundred ninety nine.
所以如果它是一个地址，你不需要说五千八百九十九。
No.
不。
5 just say the numbers if it's an address 5 8 9 9 Callister Boulevard a boulevard is a big road.
5 如果是地址，只需说出数字 5 8 9 9 Callister Boulevard 林荫大道是一条大路。
Boulevard.
大道。
OK.
好的。
Callister Boulevard De Moyne the Moyne.
Callister Boulevard De Moyne the Moyne。
This is pronounced do Moin.
这发音为do Moin。
I know it looks like death's Moin is but it's pronounced de.
我知道它看起来像死亡的Moin，但它的发音是de。
And then Moy in Des Moines Des Moines Iowa.
然后是爱荷华州得梅因的 Moy。
So in America states always have two letters.
所以在美国，各州总是有两个字母。
It's a kind of an.
这是一种。
It's a special abbreviation.
这是一个特殊的缩写。
It's a special sort of code.
这是一种特殊的代码。
For example I come from Ohio and that one is O H New York is NY.
例如，我来自俄亥俄州，那个是 O H New York is NY。
OK.
好的。
So Iowa is I.
所以爱荷华州就是我。
A.
一个。
Des Moines Iowa.
爱荷华州得梅因。
They're all different.
他们都是不同的。
There are 50.
有50个。
OK then you have the zip code.
好的，那么你有邮政编码。
DES MOINES Iowa 7 8 5 5 4.
得梅因爱荷华州 7 8 5 5 4。
So you also read this one just like the street.
因此，您也像在街上一样阅读此书。
You don't say seven the eight thousand five hundred fifty four.
你不说七八千五百五十四。
Just say the number.
只说号码。
So that's how you would read addresses and that's how you would include the abbreviations notice for
这就是您阅读地址的方式，也是您包含缩写通知的方式
the abbreviations we say the whole thing usually for apps.
我们所说的缩写通常用于应用程序。
We don't because it's so common to shorten it for acronyms we don't.
我们不这样做是因为将它缩短为我们不使用的首字母缩略词很常见。
Because that's the reason we make the acronym because it's shorter.
因为这就是我们使用首字母缩略词的原因，因为它更短。
But for most abbreviations we'll say the whole word.
但是对于大多数缩写，我们会说整个单词。
All right.
好的。
So we've covered a lot in this lesson we've covered how to say dates we've covered how to talk about
因此，我们在本课中涵盖了很多内容 我们已经涵盖了如何说日期 我们已经涵盖了如何谈论
addresses abbreviations acronyms numbers symbols things in order.
地址 缩写 首字母缩略词 数字 符号 按顺序排列。
We've talked about a lot of things including math problems a lot in this lesson.
在本课中，我们讨论了很多东西，包括数学问题。
And the best way to really practice it is to look out for it.
真正练习它的最好方法就是留意它。
And when you see it the things that we went over in this lesson whether it's a long number or a Web
当你看到我们在本课中讨论过的东西时，无论是长数字还是网络
site U.R.L. or an email address or the address of some place or an abbreviation anything related to
网站 U.R.L.或电子邮件地址或某个地方的地址或任何相关的缩写
what we talked about a symbol that's used.
我们谈到了一个使用的符号。
Speak it out loud.
大声说出来。
That's the best way for you to get used to saying it.
这是让你习惯说它的最好方式。
One of the problems with these is not that they're hard but it's that it's hard to do it quickly and
这些问题之一不是它们很难，而是很难快速完成并且
when we say these things things that are related to technical descriptions it's tough to say it quickly
当我们说这些与技术描述有关的事情时，很难说得很快
it's tough to get it out.
很难把它弄出来。
So you have to do it a lot.
所以你必须做很多。
And the best way to do it is just to practice next time you type in it.
最好的方法就是在下次输入时练习。
You are all quickly say it out loud.
你们都快大声说出来。
OK.
好的。
That's the best way to actually get the feeling for it.
这是真正获得感觉的最佳方式。
The best way to get comfortable with it.
最好的方式来适应它。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
See you in the next lesson.
下节课见。